joomfreak.com 2017-06-06

# Privacy policy - joomfreak | Free Joomla!® templates and extensions

### Protecting your privacy

Your **privacy** is **important** to us. joomfreak pledges to be responsible when gathering your personal information and to protect your privacy. This **Privacy Policy** should answer your questions about the sources and kinds of information we collect, how we use it, when it may be shared with others, and how we safeguard its confidentiality and security. We also provide you with ways to correct the data you provide us and to limit our sharing of this data with third parties. joomfreak reserves the right to modify or update this Privacy Policy at any time without prior notice. If we modify or update our Privacy Policy, we will post the revised policy here, and any modifications will apply to all information collected by joomfreak, including previously collected information.

### Who we are

**joomfreak** is a [non-profit project](http://www.joomfreak.com/ "joomfreak!") of Kreatif GmbH, which is a company with limited liability based in Bolzano (BZ), Italy. Vat number IT02596800215.

### Information we collect and how we collect it

In order to facilitate your travel, and manage our business, we may collect and maintain personal information about you. joomfreak may collect customer information from many sources to understand and meet your needs. We may collect personal information about you from:

  * You, when you voluntarily provide us with information
  * Your browser, when you visit our websites and your browser interacts with us
  * Other sources, in connection with providing your needs and services

The personal information we may collect about you through these various sources may include, but is not limited to:

  * Name, addresses and telephone numbers
  * E-mail addresses, fax numbers and pager numbers
  * Account information
  * Personal information provided via survey, focus group or other marketing research efforts
  * Personal information provided to travel agents and/or customer-service representatives to facilitate travel or other services on our member carriers

### Aggregate information

In addition to obtaining your personal information, when you use our sites, we may collect tracking information such as your browser type, the type of operating system you use, the name of your Internet service provider, and pages visited on the sites. joomfreak gets this information by using technologies, including cookies to increase the functionality and user-friendliness of our sites and to better tailor our sites to our visitors' needs. None of this tracking information identifies you personally; we collect it for reporting onsite activity in the aggregate. For example, we may want to know how long the average user spends on our sites or which pages or features get the most attention.

### What this Privacy Policy does not apply to

Corporate information (unless it is also about any identifiable person)  
Other websites accessed through a link from our websites. In this case the Privacy Policy of the owner of the linked website will apply.

### Links

Our websites contain links to other sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the content or privacy practices of those sites. We encourage you to read the privacy statements of each site that collects information from you. joomfreak's Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by joomfreak.

### Notice to/regarding children under the age of 16

If you are under 16 years of age, you should not provide any personally identifiable information (for example, your last name, home address or e-mail address) to joomfreak without the knowledge and permission of your parent or guardian. If joomfreak learns that you are under 16 years of age, joomfreak will not maintain or use any personally identifiable information about you without the verifiable consent of your parent or guardian, except as allowed by law. This may mean that you will be unable to participate in some activities on the sites without that verifiable consent. joomfreak believes that children using the Internet require special protection, and we urge parents or guardians to explain Internet safety to their children. Parents are urged to spend time online with their children to become familiar with the types of content available on the joomfreak websites and the Internet in general. Control tools are available from online services and software manufacturers to help create a safer environment for children.

### How your information will be used

We use your personal information to improve our client's product and service needs.

### Who we share your personal information with

We will not sell your name or other private profile information to third parties, and do not intend to do so in the future. From time to time, we may engage third parties to process information on our behalf and in doing so, we may share your personal information with these third parties; however, joomfreak requires that these third parties comply with joomfreak's privacy policy and principles when using and/or processing this information. We may share anonymous, non-personal aggregated information about all our users with third parties.  
If you indicate that you wish to receive promotional offers, joomfreak may also send you promotional offers in connection with its promotional partners.

### How joomfreak uses cookies and similar technologies

joomfreak uses cookies, tags, and other similar technologies as a means of collecting non-sensitive information on general websites usage so that we may improve your experience on our websites. These cookies are not designed to identify you personally and the information they gather is used only to guide improvements in navigation, enhance content and provide a means for us to ensure that our websites continue to meet sites users' needs. These cookies are not used for any promotional purposes. If you would like to browse the joomfreak websites you may do so without accepting cookies.

### How to find out what information we have concerning you and with whom we have shared it

At any time, you can find out what personal information we have, what it is being used for and to whom it has been disclosed. We will do our best to provide the required information to you within a reasonable time period and will provide an explanation if we are unable to meet your request.

### Change of inaccurate personal information

Simply contact the Privacy Officer at the address below and indicate which information is incorrect. We will correct inaccurate or incomplete information within a reasonable time and will notify you when we have done so. In the unlikely event we have given incorrect information to others, including our member carriers, we will ensure they are advised of the required corrections.

### How long do we keep your personal information?

We only keep your personal information on file for as long as we need it to provide you with service and to meet legal requirements. When we no longer need the information, it is either destroyed or made anonymous.

### Safeguards to keep your personal information confidential

We have implemented procedures and installed equipment to safeguard the security and confidentiality of your information. We continually review and improve these arrangements to ensure that we are doing all that is reasonably and technically feasible at this time to protect your information. Only those employees who need personal information to provide service have access to it. It is a condition of employment that all joomfreak employees conform to our Privacy Policy and promise to observe the highest standards of confidentiality for each customer's personal information.

### Questions, concerns or complaints relating to your privacy

If you have any questions, concerns or complaints about the way in which your personal information is collected or used by joomfreak please contact the Privacy Officer at:  
Kreatif GmbH  
J.-Kravoglstr. 14  
I-39100 Bolzano (BZ), Italy  

All inquiries or concerns relating to personal information will receive prompt attention and be acknowledged within five business days.

### If you do not want joomfreak to contact you for promotional purposes

We only contact you regarding promotional opportunities if you indicate your desire to receive offers from joomfreak. A third party may act on joomfreak's behalf and conduct a promotion for joomfreak or assist joomfreak in managing its marketing database. If you have indicated that you wish to receive promotional offers from joomfreak, you may opt out of receiving future joomfreak e-mail, telephone and postal marketing communications by contacting joomfreak at:  
Kreatif GmbH  
J.-Kravoglstr. 14  
I-39100 Bolzano (BZ), Italy  

If you have questions about removing your name from any of our subscription lists, you may contact joomfreak at [info@joomfreak.com](mailto:info@joomfreak.com). Please allow five business days for any changes to take effect.

* * *

### Google Analytics

This Website uses Google Analytics, a web analytics service provided by Google, Inc. (“Google”). Google Analytics uses “cookies”, which are text files placed on your computer, to help us analyse how users use the Website. The information generated by the cookie about your use of the Website (including your truncated IP address) will be transmitted to and stored by Google on servers in the United States. Google will use this information for the purpose of evaluating your use of the Website, compiling reports on website activity and providing other services relating to website activity and Internet usage. Google may also transfer this information to third parties where required to do so by law, or where such third parties process the information on Google's behalf. Google will not associate your IP address with any other data held by Google. By using the Website, you consent to the processing of data about you by Google in the manner and for the purposes set out above.

For more information about Google Analytics, including Google’s privacy policy, please visit http://www.google.com/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html.

If you would like to stop your data being sent to Google for analytics purposes, you can install the Google Analytics Browser Add-On, details of which are available at <http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en>.

Given the general discussion regarding the use of analysis tools with complete IP-addresses, we would like to inform you that this website is using Google Analytics with the extension "_anonymizeIp()" which means that IP-addresses are only processed in a shortened manner to prevent any direct personal references.

### Facebook Plug-ins

On our websites we use social plugins (“Plugins“) of the social network facebook.com, run by the Facebook Inc., 1601 S. California Ave, Palo Alto, CA 94304, USA (“Facebook”). The plugins are marked with the Facebook logo (white “f” on a blue tile, or a “thumbs up” sign) or with the addition of “Facebook social plugin”. The Facebook social plugins can be found at:[ http://developers.facebook.com/plugins](http://developers.facebook.com/plugins)

If you visit one of our websites that contains a facebook plugin, your browser will connect with the Facebook’s servers. Facebook transmits the contents of the plugin directly to your browser and will in return be integrated in the website by the browser. Therefore we have no influence as to the amount of data that are collected by Facebook using this plugins and want to inform you according to our knowledge: By integrating the plugin Facebook receives information that you have visited the according page of our websites. If you are logged in at facebook.com, Facebook can assign your visit to your personal Facebook account. If you interact with the plugins, for example by pressing the “like me” button or by commenting, the corresponding information is sent directly from your browser to Facebook and stored there. If you are not member of Facebook, it is nevertheless possible that Facebook detects and stores your IP address.

You learn more about the purpose and scope of this data collection, further processing and use of data and your rights and settings options to protect your data in the privacy notes of Facebook at <http://www.facebook.com/policy.php>.

### Use of Google “+1”-Button

Each time you visit a website of your internet presence which is provided with a "+1" button this will cause the browser used by you to load and display the optical illustration of the "+1" button from the Google-Server. Thus the Google server is getting information about which website of our internet presence you are visiting at that moment. Google will record your browser history when a "+1" button is displayed for up to two weeks for system maintenance and troubleshooting purposes. Any further evaluation of your visit of a website of our internet presence furnished with a "+1" button does not occur.

If you activate a "+1" button while being logged in at Google+ (Google Plus), Google will collect over your Google profile information about the URL recommended by you, your IP address and other browser-related information so that your "+1"-recommendation can be stored and can be made accessible to the public. Your "+1"-recommendations can be shown on the internet as hints, together with your profile name and your photo, in Google services such as search results or your Google profile (as "+1” tab in your Google profile) or other places on websites and adverts on the internet.

At the internet address below you can find data protection remarks of Google concerning the "+1" button with more information about collection, transfer and use of data by Google to your rights as well as your profile setting options: <https://www.google.com/intl/de/+/policy/+1button.html>.
